Finding Aid for Women for Survival of Agriculture in Michigan records, 1971-1986
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Women for Survival of Agriculture in Michigan records 1971-1986
Women for Survival of Agriculture in Michigan
0.3 linear feet
85466 Bg 2
Organization of Michigan family farm wives created in 1971. History and general organizational materials; papers relating to the informational unit of the organization, the American Agri-Women, and the national movement of family farm wives; related printed materials; and photographs.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were donated by the organization (donor no. 6865 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
This organization of Michigan family farm wives was created in 1971.
The record group consists of historical background and general organizational materials; papers relating to the informational unit of the organization, the American Agri-Women, and the national movement of family farm wives. There are also some related printed materials and photographs.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Michigan.; American Agri-Women.; Farmers--Michigan.; Women--Michigan--Societies and clubs.; Women in agriculture--Michigan.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Apples.; Clothing and dress.; Demonstrations.; Farmers' groups.; Kalamazoo (Mich.); Women for Survival of Agriculture in Michigan.; Women--Organizations.; Women--Political life.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Organizational records
  - Historical Background (Box 1)
    (folder no. 1)
  - Agendas (fragmentary) and State Board minutes, December 9, 1981 and 1984-1985 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 2)
  - Newsletters, 1972-April 1986 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 3)
  - Promotional Materials (Box 1)
    (folder no. 4)
  - Newsclippings, 1971-1981 (photocopies) (Box 1)
    (folder no. 5)
  - Newsclippings, 1972-1973 (original) (Box 1)
    (folder no. 5-A)
  - Correspondence, notices and miscellaneous, ca. 1972-1981 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 6)
  - WSAM: Informational Unit, ca. 1976-1977 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 7)
  - 6th National Convention of American Agri-Women and 10th Anniversary Celebration of WSAM, 1981 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 8)
  - American Agri-Women, ca. 1974-1982 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 9)
  - Other Farm Women's Groups, mostly 1982 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 10)
  - Related Printed Materials, ca. 1976 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 11)
  - Photographs of activities, particularly Kalamazoo, Michigan demonstration against meat boycott, ca. 1972-1973 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 12)